[Waco] Blossom Garden Club records, Inclusive: 1955-1972, undated, Bulk: 1955-1960
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
[Waco] Blossom Garden Club records
Inclusive: 1955-1972, undated, Bulk: 1955-1960
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
3632
[Waco] Blossom Garden Club
2 document boxes.
The [Waco] Blossom Garden Club records contain scrapbooks and photographs generated by the club during the mid-twentieth century.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Poor.
Biography/Profile
The [Waco] Blossom Garden Club was a part of a larger network of garden clubs in Waco during the twentieth century and was associated with both the Waco Council of Garden Clubs and District V of Texas Garden Clubs, Inc. Among other activities, the organization hosted a circus themed flower show, entitled "The Greatest Show on Earth," in April 1957.
Scope and Content
The [Waco] Blossom Garden Club records consist of materials from the 1950's through the 1970's, with some undated items. The records display the activities of the club, particularly their participation in flower shows.
Series I, Publicity/Press, contains photographs and scrapbooks.
Arrangement
The collection was partially processed into two series: I. Yearbooks and II. Scrapbooks.
Currently, the collection resides in one series: I. Publicity/Press.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 3632. Acquired 2005-05-06
Index Terms
Places
Waco (Tex.) -- History -- 20th Century.
Subjects
Gardening -- Texas -- McLennan County.; Gardening -- Texas -- Waco -- Societies, etc.; Women -- Texas -- Waco -- Societies and clubs.
Genres
Photographs.; Scrapbooks.
- Publicity/Press, 1955-1971, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Poor.
  Biography/Profile
  The series contains photographs and scrapbooks. The series is in poor condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photograph album; Photographic print
  - Loose Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Award-22 Christmas Show Scrapbook (1 of 3), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Award-22 Christmas Show Scrapbook (2 of 3), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Award-22 Christmas Show Scrapbook (3 of 3), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Happiness is Christ-Mass Scrapbook, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A Floral Symphony Scrapbook #1, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - A Floral Symphony Scrapbook #2 (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - A Floral Symphony Scrapbook #2 (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Circus Scrapbook #1 (1 of 5), 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Circus Scrapbook #1 (2 of 5), 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Circus Scrapbook #1 (3 of 5), 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Circus Scrapbook #1 (4 of 5), 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Circus Scrapbook #1 (5 of 5), 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Circus Scrapbook #2 (1 of 3), 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Circus Scrapbook #2 (2 of 3), 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Circus Scrapbook #2 (3 of 3), 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 11)